Guide to the Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records, 1936-ongoing UA.09.05.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Office of Student Activities and Facilities records
1936-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Office of Student Activities and Facilities
UA.09.05.0001
65.5 Linear Feet
23 Megabytes
The Duke University Office of Student Activities and Facilities (OSAF) serves as a liaison between the university administration and student groups, clubs, and organizations. The Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records, 1936-ongoing, contain correspondence, charters, directories, annual reports, financial statements, and other information on Duke University student organizations, including Duke Student Government, Associated Students of Duke University, the Undergraduate Publications board, the Duke University Union, and the Office of University Life. The OSAF Records also document Duke University student life more generally, including their social life, customs, and political activity.
Access Restrictions
Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
Provenance
The Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer from 1978-2014.
Historical Note
The Duke University Office of Student Activities and Facilities (OSAF) serves as a liaison between the university administration and student groups, clubs, and organizations. OSAF also has an advising component, serving recognized student organizations at Duke University. In 2012, OSAF merged with Event Management and changed its name to University Center Activities & Events (UCAE).
Collection Overview
The Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records, 1936-ongoing, contain correspondence, charters, directories, annual reports, financial statements, and other detailed information on many Duke University student organizations, including Duke Student Government (DSG), Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), the Undergraduate Publications board, the Duke University Union, and the Office of University Life. In addition to documenting the histories of specific on-campus groups, the OSAF Records provide a wealth of material on Duke University students in general, including but not limited to their social life, political activity, and changing social customs throughout the 20th century.
Arrangement: unless stated otherwise, all accessions are arranged as received, generally in alphabetical order.
Related Material
Because the Office of Student Activities and Facilities Records contain a sampling of documents from many Duke University student groups that span several decades, the collection complements many others already held in the University Archives. The following is a short but not exhaustive list of related collections that can be accessed at the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library. Additional materials can be found by searching the online catalog for the names of individual groups, university offices, residential houses, and fraternities and sororities.
Associated Students of Duke University Records, 1965 - 1993, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Duke Artists Series records, 1931-2000, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Duke Student Government Records, 1983 - 2008, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Fraternities and Sororities collection, 1931-2001,
Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Major Attractions Committee records, 1957-1995,
Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Major Speakers Committee, 1956-1985,
Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Student Organizations Reference Collection, 1913-ongoing,
Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Undergraduate Publications Board records, 1911-1997,
Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Conditions Governing Access
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Conditions Governing Access
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
College students -- Political activity -- North Carolina -- Durham; College students -- North Carolina -- Durham -- Conduct of life; Duke University. Undergraduate Publications Board; Duke University -- History -- 20th century; Duke University. Union; Duke University. Student Government; Associated Students of Duke University; Duke University. Office of University Life; Duke University. Office of Student Activities and Facilities; Duke University. Office of Student Activities and Facilities; Duke University -- Students; Duke University -- Students -- Societies, etc.; Duke University -- Students -- Social life and customs
- Accession UA 78-114, 1957-1970, 1 folders
  Scope and Contents note
  Officer rosters, correspondence, and financial data for approximately thirty student interest groups and houses. Also included are financial statements for two ad hoc groups apparently formed into reaction to contemporaneous world political events: Fast for Biafra, 1969; and Hungarian Student Aid Drive, 1957. For other generally-related manuscript materials in the Rubenstein Library, see also the Hungarian Revolution, 1956: miscellaneous pamphlets and clippings.
  - Various organizations--officers, correspondence, and financial data, 1957-1970 (Box 1)
- Accession UA 81-120, 1936-1949, 8 folders
  Eight bound volumes of annual reports spanning thirteen years; some volumes combine multiple years, but fiscal years 1937/38, 1938/39, and 1941/42 are not represented. Volumes are generally entitled as some variant of Report of the Office of Student Activities & Report of the Staff of Quadrangle Pictures. Group portraits of Quadrangle Pictures officers are tipped into volumes preceding 1941.
  - Annual Reports--Office of Student Activities, Quadrangle Pictures, and other groups, 1936-1949, 8 folders (Box 1)
- Accession UA 81-122, 1937-1978, 6 boxes
  Files on approximately 150 student groups and related topics about campus life. Materials date mainly from 1955-1978, with two exceptions: the folder groups "Student Office-Holders" and "Ledgers (disbound)," both described in more detail at their folder entries below. Arranged as received, except that disbound ledgers have been moved to the end of the accession.
  - The Above Ground Review, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Ad Hoc Committee of Concerned Students for Muscular Dystrophy--loan agreements, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Advancement for Women, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Affirmative Action plan, Duke University, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Society, 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - AIESEC, 1963-1971 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Phi Omega, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association (APGA), 1974-1976, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Angel Flight Constitution, undated (Box 1)
  - Apartment guide, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Appalachian State University: policies for student organizations, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Archive--current year, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - The Arion, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Arnold Air Society, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1962-1972, 14 folders
    - Almanac, 1971-1972 (Box 1)
    - Budget Commission, 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 1)
    - Chartering Procedure, 1962-1972, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Elections and Organization, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Executive Meeting Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - General, 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Legislature, 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Association Independent Houses, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Association of African Students (AAS), 1970-1976 (Box 1)
  - Bassett Fund, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - Bench and Bar Society, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Black Student Alliance (BSA), 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Black students, miscellaneous, 1966-1975, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Blue Jeans, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Campus Christian Life Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Celestial Omnibus, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
  - Chanticleer, 1968-1971, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Chartered organizations, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Chisholm, Shirley, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Chronicle--miscellaneous and business operations, 1964-1970, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - CIRUNA, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Class of 1970, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Committee of Responsibility, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Committee on Contraception and Abortion, 1970-1974 (Box 2)
  - Community volunteer opportunities, 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Constitutions, organizations (defunct), 1958-1971 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence--miscellaneous, 1956-1965, 5 folders (Box 2)
  - DUAA Budget, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Due to Circumstances Beyond Our Control, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Duke Engineer, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Duke Outing Club, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Duke Peer--current year, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Duke Players, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Directory, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Marching Band (DUMB), 1970-1973, 7 folders (Box 2)
    Atlanta trips, clippings, DUMBugle (newsletter), marching formations, logos, roster, and general files.
  - Duke University Pep Board, 1955-1970 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Print Shop, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Sports Car Club, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Duke University Undergraduate Journal, 1970 (Box 2)
  - ECOS, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Engineer Student Government, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Epworth, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Eta Kappa Nu, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Fellowship of Christian Athletes--miscellaneous, 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Steering Committee, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Film Society, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Financial statements--student organizations and scattered memos, 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Foreign Student Committee, 1958-1965 (Box 3)
  - Forms, applications, policies, regulations, 1974-1976 (Box 3)
  - Founders' Day, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Freshman house accounts, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Freshman orientation week, 1957-1964 (Box 3)
  - Games room, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Gilbert, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Graduate Center, 1961-1971, 4 folders (Box 3)
  - Graduate Student Association, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Greeks--Duke University Women's College, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Hanes Annex, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Homecoming, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Honor Societies, Association of College, 1967 (Box 3)
  - Hoof 'n' Horn, 1964-1968, 3 folders (Box 3)
  - House counselors, 1970 (Box 3)
  - House G--freshmen, 1969 (Box 3)
  - House P, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Information Center--correspondence and miscellaneous, 1954-1965 (Box 3)
  - Inter-Dormitory Council, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Inter-Fraternity Council (IFC)--concerts and miscellaneous, 1963-1970, 5 folders (Box 3)
  - International Club, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Inter-Varsity Christian Fellowship, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Job Planning and Achievement Review, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Kappa Delta Pi--miscellaneous, 1964-1966 (Box 3)
  - Karate Club, circa 1970 (Box 3)
  - Lost and found, 1957-1963, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Manual for student organizations, undated (Box 3)
  - Men's Chorus, 1965-1969, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Men's Glee Club, 1964-1970, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Men's Student Government Association, 1964-1967, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Mirecourt, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Movement for Shared Authority, 1975 (Box 3)
  - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators (NASPA)--bulletins and journals, 1972-1976, 3 folders (Box 3)
  - National Student Association, 1959-1972, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Newman Club--miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 3)
  - NROTC Unit Commodore Club, 1964-1967 (Box 3)
  - NSGA (nursing), 1970-1974 (Box 3)
  - Obscenity--policy on publication (other schools), 1968 (Box 3)
  - Off-campus manuals, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Officers and financial statements, 1964-1969 (Box 3)
  - Officers--presidents and treasurers of organizations, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
  - Omnicron Delta Kappa, 1964-1967 (Box 3)
  - Personnel records: Student Activities, other (misc.), 1969-1974 (Box 3)
  - Phi Eta Sigma, 1963-1970 (Box 3)
  - Photography Club (inactive), 1951-1952 (Box 3)
  - Phi Mu Epsilon (misc.), 1963-1968 (Box 3)
  - Pi Mu Epsilon--treasury, 1967-1973 (Box 3)
  - Pi Sigma Alpha (misc.), 1964-1970 (Box 3)
  - Pi Tau Sigma, 1967-1969 (Box 3)
  - Pickets and Protest Regulations (other schools), 1968-1969 (Box 3)
  - Playbill--current year, 1965-1968 (Box 3)
  - Political Science Union, undated (Box 3)
  - Praxis/Socialist Action Union, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Pre-Medical Society, 1960-1968 (Box 3)
  - Presidents of organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Professional concerns, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Publications Board, 1965-1970 (Box 3)
  - Publishing (copy to Mr. Douglas Jensen), 1968-1970 (Box 3)
  - Quadrangle Federation, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Racism, reports on, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
  - Radio Council, 1964-1971 (Box 3)
  - Red Friars, 1965-1970 (Box 3)
  - Residential life, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Residential living, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Rubbish, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Sigma Delta Pi, 1965-1967 (Box 4)
  - Sigma Pi Sigma, 1964-1967 (Box 4)
  - Soccer Club, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Steering Committee for University Weekends, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
  - Student Activities, 1961-1975, 7 folders (Box 4)
    Financial statements, organizational loans, van usage, and various forms and regulations.
  - Student Fees, 1969-1976 (Box 4)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), 1970 (Box 4)
  - Student legal aid, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Student Liberation Front (PRAXIS), 1964-1970 (Box 4)
  - Student Office-Holders, 1887-1937, 29 folders
    Although apparently compiled in 1937, the lists in this folder group cite officers of various clubs and organizations as early as the late 1880s. In addition to documenting the histories of various campus groups, the folders contain extensive demographic data about the student body spanning several decades, since student officers' home addresses are given in most cases. The folder "Class Officers" contains "A Tentative List of Student Organizations and Enterprises, Trinity College and Duke University, 1846-1937," a compilation of some 400 student organizations from the first century of the university's history.
    - Athletics, 1894-1937 (Box 4)
    - Chemistry, 1913-1925 (Box 4)
    - Civic, 1911-1937 (Box 4)
    - Class officers, 1919-1937 (Box 4)
    - Classical Studies, 1910-1937 (Box 4)
    - Commerce and Economics, 1932-1937 (Box 4)
    - Dramatics, 1923-1937 (Box 4)
    - Education, 1926-1937 (Box 4)
    - Engineering, 1913-1937 (Box 4)
    - Fictitious, 1928-1936 (Box 4)
    - Forensics, 1888-1937 (Box 4)
    - Fraternities, 1935-1937 (Box 4)
    - Geographical, 1911-1937 (Box 4)
    - History, 1911-1917 (Box 4)
    - Hobby, 1920-1937 (Box 4)
    - Honorary, 1916-1937 (Box 4)
    - Journalistic, 1912-1913 (Box 4)
    - Language, 1908-1937 (Box 4)
    - Legal, 1929-1937 (Box 4)
    - Literary, 1911-1926 (Box 4)
    - Military, 1917-1921 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1938 (Box 4)
    - Musical, 1908-1937 (Box 4)
    - Political, 1918-1937 (Box 4)
    - Publications, 1887-1937 (Box 4)
    - Religious and Theological, 1888-1937 (Box 4)
    - Scholastic, 1920-1937 (Box 4)
    - Scientific, 1908-1937 (Box 4)
    - Sororities, 1920-1937 (Box 4)
  - Student organizations, 1963-1975, 10 folders (Box 4)
    Audited statements, financial reports and procedures, and miscellaneous files.
  - Student Perspective--the student philosophy, 1964 (Box 4)
  - Student press, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Student protest, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Student protest--Duke vigil, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Student protests--other campuses, 1967-1969 (Box 4)
  - Student Union, 1965-1969 (Box 4)
  - Student Union procedural reports, 1962-1965 (Box 4)
  - Sub-committee on Non-Curricular Life--reports, undated (Box 4)
  - Summer activities, 1970 (Box 4)
  - Supplies, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Symposium Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 4)
  - Tabard Hall, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Taylor Hall, 1968-1970 (Box 4)
  - Theta Alpha Phi, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Town Men's Club, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Transfer and off-campus programming, 1971-1974 (Box 4)
  - Transfer students, circa 1974 (Box 4)
  - Union Political Party--miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 4)
  - University budget, 1974-1976 (Box 4)
  - University self-study, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
  - Wargamers, 1967 (Box 4)
  - WDBS radio station, 1967-1970 (Box 4)
  - Windsor Federation Fund, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Work samples, 1965-1968, 17 folders (Box 5)
    Copies of leaflets, charts, flyers, organizational papers, minutes, and other documents printed by the Student Activities Office for various student organizations and events. Coverage of campus life is particularly rich for the 1967-1968 academic year.
  - YMCA--miscellaneous, 1963-1970, 2 folders (Box 5)
  - YMCA MOBE (National Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam), 1969 (Box 5)
  - YMCA--printed materials, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - YMCA--Project Bolivia, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
  - Young Democrat Club, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Young Republican Club, 1966-1971 (Box 5)
  - Ledgers (disbound): Student Activities Operating Account, 1939-1942, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Ledgers (disbound): Student Activities Operating Account, 1942-1952, 4 folders (Box 6)
  - Ledgers (disbound): Student Activities Operating Account, 1952-1957, 3 folders (Box 6)
- Accession UA 82-36, 1978-1980, 1 folders
  Folder of miscellaneous financial and other information on several organizations, including the Bassett Fund and the Black Student Alliance among others.
  - Various organizations--correspondence, financial records, and printed materials, 1978-1980 (Box 7)
- Accession UA 82-58, 1955-1980, 5 boxes
  Acc. UA 82-58 also includes the former UA 81-49. Office files of Carolyn Gray, former Director of Student Activities. Mostly correspondence and financial information about student organizations at Duke.
  - ABC (A Better Chance) Weekend, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Accident reports, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Accounting and M.S. Majors Union charter file --- permanent, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
  - Accounting notices, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
  - Agenda, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - American Indians at Duke (A.I.D.), 1977 (Box 7)
  - Alliance Against Racism and Political Repression--budget file, 1976 (Box 7)
  - American College Personnel Association (ACPA)--correspondence, newsletters, and Women's Task Force, 1975-1979, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - American Personnel and Guidance Association (APGA), 1976-1979 (Box 7)
  - Another Drama Group, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Applicants for office space, 1976-1979 (Box 7)
  - Application permanent reserve, 1979-1980 (Box 7)
  - Archive information, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Art Majors' Union, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1968-1980, 15 folders
    - Budget, 1971-1979, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Constitution, 1968-1977 (Box 7)
    - Financial reports, 1974-1980 (Box 7)
    - Funding, 1975-1979 (Box 7)
    - Legislature, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
    - Minutes of the ASDU Legislature Meeting, 1972-1978 (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1969, 5 folders (Box 7)
    - Summary reports of ASDU activities, 1974-1975 (Box 7)
  - Association of African Students (AAS)--Black Week 1972 and miscellaneous files, 1972-1976 (Box 7)
  - Astronomy Club--charter file and loan agreement, 1973-1975 (Box 7)
  - Authorization for complimentary tickets, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Auto Owners Club, undated (Box 7)
  - Automix Keyboards, Inc. (AKI), 1974-1976 (Box 7)
  - Bassett Committee, 1971-1979 (Box 7)
  - Belly Dance Association--budget file, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Beta Theta Pi correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 7)
  - Beta Theta Pi (Gamma Rho chapter)--loan agreement, 1975-1977 (Box 7)
  - Billiards Club, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Black Affairs, Office of--conference, minutes, and miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 7)
  - Black Student Alliance (BSA), 1976-1980, 4 folders (Box 7)
    Correspondence, charter file, programming, and other materials.
  - Black student roster and programming ideas, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
  - Black Student Weekend, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
  - Black/White discussion groups, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Blue Jeans charter file, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Cable TV project, 1976-1978 (Box 7)
  - Camera Corner, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ, 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - Car rental correspondence, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Center for Tension Control--charter file, 1977-1978 (Box 7)
  - Chairmen of departments, 1975-1979 (Box 7)
  - Chanticleer, 1970-1979, 5 folders (Box 8)
    Photography bids and specifications, printing and publishing, and other materials.
  - Chapel, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Charter flights, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Checks--D.U. returned check account, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
  - Chess Club--charter file (permanent), 1970-1976 (Box 8)
  - Chi Delta Chapter of Psi Upsilon fraternity--loan agreement, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Chronicle, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Co-curricular transcript, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Codes--agency funds and Student Activities agency codes, 1968-1977 (Box 8)
  - Codes-new and old accounts, 1975-1979 (Box 8)
  - Collegiate Civitan and Collegiate Civitan International, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Comparative Area Studies Union--charter file, permanent, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Contemporary Fiction Group--charter file, permanent, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence--In, 1974-1979, 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Correspondence--miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box 8)
  - Correspondence--Out, 1971-1979, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Cricket Club--charter file, permanent, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Delta Sigma Phi, 1973-1975 (Box 8)
  - De Tocqueville Society, 1973-1975 (Box 8)
  - Discipleship Training Class--charter file, permanent, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Divine Meditation Organization--charter file, permanent, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Duke Broadcasting, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Duke Christian fellowship--inter-varsity, 1968-1974 (Box 8)
  - Duke Committee for Economic Justice, 1976-1978 (Box 8)
  - Duke Composition Shop--applicants and bids, 1974-1976 (Box 8)
  - Duke Composition Shop--miscellaneous, 1974-1977 (Box 8)
  - Duke Cyclists' League, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Duke Dance Club--charter file, 1972-1978 (Box 8)
  - Duke Independent Women--record of charter, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Duke Summer Daycamp, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Calendar, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Chorale, 1971-1978 (Box 8)
  - Duke University Union, 1971-1979 (Box 8)
  - Durham Community Learning Exchange, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
  - Dymo Graphic Systems, Inc., 1976 (Box 8)
  - East Campus Center Committee, 1968-1976 (Box 8)
  - Eckankar--charter file, permanent, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Educational Facilities Committee: "A Proposal for the Scope, Site, and Budget for Duke University Union, 1971 (Box 8)
  - El Circulo Hispano--charter file, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Elon College newspaper: The Pendulum, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Employee concerns, 1974-1975 (Box 8)
  - Equal Opportunity Office, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Equipment, 1974-1976 (Box 8)
  - Extended Student Affairs staff, 1973-1976 (Box 8)
  - Facilities: 214 Old Chemistry, 1970-1976 (Box 8)
  - Facilities available to student org., East Campus: auditoriums, meeting rooms, etc., 1970-1975 (Box 8)
  - Facilities available to student org.--PA Systems, table, etc., 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Facilities available to student org., West Campus: auditoriums, meeting rooms, etc., 1973 (Box 8)